{
    "id": "16d4b3cdb59649ed923a585f31bc221d",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Could you translate this document .............. German for me?",
            "description": "Translate is followed by into, not in or to.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "into",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You remind me ................... my cousin.",
            "description": "Remind is followed by of. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He wasn't very nice ....................... me when we met last week.",
            "description": "To talk about people's attitude, we use nice to. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This perfume is typical ...................... the region.",
            "description": "After typical we use of, not for.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Her marriage ..................... James didn't last very long.",
            "description": "Marriage is followed by to. Also, we get married to somebody. ",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He married .................. childhood sweetheart.",
            "description": "You marry somebody. No preposition is used in this expression. ",
            "answers": [
                "his",
                "to his",
                "with his"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will ............................. the drinks.",
            "description": "We pay somebody and pay for something. ",
            "answers": [
                "pay",
                "pay for",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Everybody was surprised ..................... the weather.",
            "description": "Surprise can be followed by 'at' or 'by'.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "by",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I tripped ......................... the  bags and fell on the platform.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The customs are searching .................... drugs at the airport.",
            "description": "To search for something is to look for it. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "No preposition is required"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We had a ........................ philosophy.",
            "description": "Discussion is followed by about. ",
            "answers": [
                "discussion",
                "discussion of",
                "discussion about"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We have just entered .................... an agreement with them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "into",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}